The kettle and the idol
Well, that's how it's ending early.
Please let us know if you have any news from Harima-san.
Yes, I'm Harimakana. I, Harima Kana, deliver showroom delivery and hashtag Harichannel every Thursday at 8 pm.
If you have time, I would be very happy if you could come and watch. We are also on social networking sites,
We are also on social networking sites such as Instagram, Twitter, and TikTok,
I would be very happy if you could take this opportunity to follow me.
I would appreciate it if you could take this opportunity to follow me.
Thank you very much.
I heard that the showroom has been very well received,
Yes.
I have heard that.
Thank you very much. I'm glad to hear that.
I'm sure you have a point,
A plot?
Like a song in a certain place.
But that's important enough, so we'll fill it in from there.
Yes.
After this, you will continue to work on the stage and other things.
Yes, that's right. I would like to do some singing this year,
I'm thinking of doing a solo live concert by myself in the summer.
A solo concert by yourself in the summer?
Is that OK? I'm sorry, but I'm not sure.
You're okay with that, right?
Yes.
I'm thinking of doing a "live" show.
Thank you very much. I am looking forward to it.
Can I give Haruma a gift from Yabana? I am thinking about it. Thank you very much. I am looking forward to it.
May I give Harima a present from Yagan-kun at the end?
I'm so happy!
I'm Yagan, and I'd like to give you this tea,
I prepared jasmine tea for you today.
I'm so happy!
I know you have been working hard on the play and sugar, so I thought it would be natural for you to have this tea,
I think you are used to having a lot of sugar in your throat, so I thought it would be natural for you,
I have prepared a jasmine tea with a refreshing aroma that will spread in your mouth.
Please drink it.
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
Do you drink tea on a regular basis? I drink a lot of tea. I like tea. Good. Do you drink tea on a regular basis?
I drink a lot of tea. I like tea.
I see.
That's an interesting point. This story.
I'm glad. I'm glad.
How's it going?
Tea, then.
I'm sorry.
I'll watch. I'll finish it.
So you said it?
Are you afraid of pauses?
I'm a little afraid of pauses.
That's right. You are too service-oriented. Are you okay?
Thank you very much.
This program is chaired by Mr. Haruyama.
Is that right?
That's right. He's the star of the show.
It's a big space. It's a big place. Is it? Yes, it is. It's the star of the show.
It's a big place.
What? I'm so happy!
It's spacious.
It's the center.
At last. Thank you very much. I'm glad.
You're so persistent.
I was surprised.
I was surprised to see you on the side and not in the eye anymore.
Is that possible? The clients.
Well, well, well. They pay attention to you.
Yes. The attention is different, you know.
Yes. Well then, Mr. Harima.
Yes. Lastly, the cutest person in the program.
You are not so good at this, are you?
Can I ask you to close the show for the camera?
Please say bye-bye at the end.
That's it. Names are bye-bye, aren't they?
I know it's "bye-bye," but don't you get a lot of comments when you've been an idol for this long?
All the time.
Try saying something.
I'm always told "No.
Of course.
Yes.Yes, by all means.
By all means.
Yes, by all means. I understand.
Uh, yah.
What?
New material?
No, no, no.
Don't drop me here.
No, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's like...
It's Mr. Ryusei.
I'm so nervous.
It's okay. It's okay.
Here you go.
Here we go.
I'll be happy if you like Harima more.
Kana Harima
This is Kana Harima.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
This program,
Nanosan
Toshisan
Mr. Kururun Harimashi
Sounosuke
Gorotei-san provided this program.
Thank you very much!